{
    "subject": "Charles_Ingalls",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Caroline_Ingalls",
    "human_readable": "Charles Ingalls is married to Caroline Ingalls.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9365976452827454,
            "question": "Who is married to Caroline Ingalls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9273195862770081,
            "question": "Is Caroline Ingalls married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9103831648826599,
            "question": "Are Charles and Caroline Ingalls a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8432591557502747,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Charles Ingalls and Caroline Ingalls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.822313129901886,
            "question": "Who is Charles Ingalls' wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8210735321044922,
            "question": "Who are Charles Ingalls and Caroline Ingalls related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361795902252197,
            "question": "Is there a familial connection between Charles and Caroline Ingalls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711496889591217,
            "question": "Is Charles Ingalls in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931648254394531,
            "question": "What is the name of Charles Ingalls' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931648254394531,
            "question": "What is the name of Charles Ingalls' spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Ingalls is married to Caroline Ingalls.",
            "html": "yago_7550_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Charles Ingalls' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_7550_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Charles Ingalls in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_7550_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a familial connection between Charles and Caroline Ingalls?",
            "html": "yago_7550_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7550_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Charles Ingalls is married to Caroline Ingalls\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances that confirm Charles Ingalls was married to Caroline Quiner, later referred to as Caroline Ingalls. In one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7550/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt), it is explicitly stated that \"At the age of 21, Caroline married Charles Ingalls...\". Another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7550/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt) also confirms their marriage."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage of Charles Ingalls and Caroline Ingalls, confirming that they were indeed married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}